PG 160, Floods and Hurricanes in Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
Floods and Hurricanes in Connecticut collection
1936-2011
bulk 1936-1955
Connecticut State Library
10 cubic feet
Hurricanes and Nor'easters can cause major flooding of the Connecticut River and its tributaries. Three of the more impressive include floods in March 1936, September, 1938 and August 1955.
PG160
Multiple
Historical Note
Hurricanes and Nor'easters can cause major flooding of the Connecticut River and its tributaries. Three of the more impressive include floods in March 1936, September, 1938 and August 1955.
Scope and Content
Consists of aerial photographs and b&w prints depicting scenes from a number of Connecticut towns.
Aerial photographs make up the bulk of the collection and include mosaic, vertical and oblique views. There are 524 views of the 1936 flood photographed by the 8th Photographic Section, US Air Corps for the US Engineer Office in Providence, RI and 132 views of the September 1938 flood and hurricane in Connecticut and Rhode Island, photographed by the 118th Photographic Section of the US Air Corps. Noteworthy are the numerous shoreline views.
Also includes 58 photographs of Naugatuck in the Flood of 1955 collectively titled "Black Friday", compiled by the Naugatuck Daily News, as well as several smaller collections.
Photocopies of photographs in the Prescott Bush papers transfered to Archives & Special Collections at The Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut in August 1991.
Also includes approximately 444 digital photographs which document damage caused by Tropical Storm Irene on August 27-28, 2011.
Arrangement
Series 1. Flood of 1936
Oblique and Vertical Views, Accession: T001765
Mosaic Views, Accession: T001862
William Hankard Collection, Accession: T001765
A.B. Grasso Collection, Accession: T001765
Hartford Public Library Collection, Accession: T001765
Harriet U. Fish Collection, Accession: T001765
Mildred Davieau Collection, Accession: T001765
Series 2. Flood of 1938
Oblique Views, Accession: T001765
Myron Johnson Collection, Accession: T001765
Midred Davieau Collection, Accession: T001765
Series 3. Flood of 1955
Towns, Accession: T001765
Black Friday, Accession: T001765
Barbara Lee Collection, Accession: T001765
Prescott Bush Papers, Accession: T001862
Anita Olson Scrapbook, Accession 2010-013
Seymour, Accession 2010-035
Ansonia, Accession 2010-040
Norwalk, Accession 2012-048
Series 4. Tropical Storm Irene, 2011
Department of Energy and Environmental Protection Photographs, Accession: 2012-018
Related Material
PG 440: Collins collection, album 3, contains views of the Colt’s Patent Fire Arms Manufacturing Co. in Hartford During the flood.
RG 089: Miscellaneous Aerial Photographs, several images of rivers after the 1955 flood.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Flood damage -- Connecticut; Floods -- Connecticut -- 20th century; Hurricane, 1938; Hurricane Diane, 1955
Places:
Ansonia (Conn.); Ashford (Conn.); Avon (Conn.); Barkhamsted (Conn.); Beacon Falls (Conn.); Branford (Conn.); Bristol (Conn.); Canaan (Conn.); Canton (Conn.); Clinton (Conn.); Cromwell (Conn.); Danbury (Conn.); Darien (Conn.); Derby (Conn.); East Granby (Conn.); East Hartford (Conn.); East Haven (Conn.); East Lyme (Conn.); Farmington (Conn.); Granby (Conn.); Groton (Conn.); Guilford (Conn.); Hartford (Conn.); Madison (Conn.); Mansfield (Conn.); Middletown (Conn.); Milford (Conn.); Naugatuck (Conn.); New Hartford (Conn.); New London (Conn.); Norfolk (Conn.); Norwalk (Conn.); Norwich (Conn.); Old Lyme (Conn.); Old Saybrook (Conn.); Putnam (Conn.); Scotland (Conn.); Simsbury (Conn.); Sprague (Conn.); Stafford (Conn.); Torrington (Conn.); Waterbury (Conn.); Waterford (Conn.); Westbrook (Conn.); Wethersfield (Conn.); Willington (Conn.); Wilton (Conn.); Windham (Conn.); Winsted (Conn.); Windsor Locks (Conn.)
Document Types:
Photographs; Compact discs
Restrictions on Access
Series 4. Tropical Storm Irene, Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP) Photographs, 2011, Accession: 2012-018, 2 compact discs, is restricted. Contact State Archives staff for assistance.
See the policy.
Provenance
The State Library purchased the 1936 photographs from the Providence Engineer Office. They were taken by the Eighth Photographic Section, U.S. Air Corps. The 43d Division of the Connecticut National Guard donated the 1938 photographs. They were taken by the 118th Photographic Section, U.S. Air Corps, Connecticut National Guard. The Naugatuck Daily News donated their photographs of the Flood of 1955, collectively titled "Black Friday", in July 1956. Janice Matthews from the Hartford Room at the Hartford Public Library donated photographs in October 1997. Other private donors of Flood of 1936 photographs include William Hankard, A.B. Grasso, Harriet U. Fish, and Mildred Davieau. Myron Johnson donated a small collection of 1938 photographs. Barbara Lee, a former Connecticut State Library employee, donated photographs of the 1955 flood showing Collinsville. Accession 2012-018 was transferred by the Department of Energy and Environmental Protection (DEEP) to the State Library in 2012. Accession 2012-048 was donated by Henry J. Deysenroth to the State Library in 2012.
Container List
- Series 1. Flood of 1936
  - Oblique Views, 1936; T001765
    Towns are listed from north to south.
    - Lyndon, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 1)
    - St. Johnsbury, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 2-8)
    - Passumsic, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 9-11)
    - Lancaster, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 12)
    - Gilman, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 13)
    - Inwood, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 14-15)
    - No. Monroe, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 16-18)
    - White Mts. N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 19-21)
    - Haverhill, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 22)
    - Piermont, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 23-24)
    - Ely, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 25-26)
    - Thetford, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 27)
    - Hanover, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 28-30)
    - Hartford, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 31)
    - White River, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 32-40)
    - Windsor, Vt. (Box 1, Envelope 41-49)
    - Claremont, N.H. (Box 1, Envelope 50)
    - Springfield, Vt. (Box 2, Envelope 51)
    - Bellows Falls, Vt. (Box 2, Envelope 52-61)
    - Walpole, N.H. (Box 2, Envelope 62-63)
    - Westmoreland, N.H. (Box 2, Envelope 64)
    - Brattleboro, Vt. (Box 2, Envelope 65-70)
    - Vernon, Vt. (Box 2, Envelope 71-74)
    - Northfield, Mass. (Box 2, Envelope 75-80)
    - Mt. Hermon, Mass. (Box 2, Envelope 81)
    - Saw Mill Creed, Mass (Box 2, Envelope 82)
    - Turners Falls, Mass. (Box 2, Envelope 83-87)
    - Millers Falls, Mass. (Box 2, Envelope 88-92)
    - Greenfield, Mass. (Box 2, Envelope 93-100)
    - Deerfield, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 101-102)
    - Montague, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 103)
    - Sunderland, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 104-106)
    - Whately, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 107-108)
    - Bradstreet, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 109)
    - Hadley, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 110)
    - Northampton, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 111-119)
    - Holyoke, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 120-129)
    - Mt. Tom - Holyoke, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 130-131)
    - Chicopee Falls, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 132-141)
    - Springfield, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 142-146)
    - Poquicknol, Mass. (Box 3, Envelope 147-149)
    - Windsor Locks, Conn. (Box 3, Envelope 150-158)
    - Hartford, Conn. (Box 3, Envelope 159-165)
    - Hartford, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 166-196)
    - East Hartford, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 197-201)
    - Salmon Brook, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 202)
    - Wethersfield, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 203)
    - Belamose, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 204)
    - Balamose, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 204)
    - Middletown, Conn. (Box 4, Envelope 206-220)
  - Vertical Views, 1836; T001765
    - St. Johnsbury, Vt. (Box 5, Envelope 1-5)
    - Woodsville, N.H. (Box 5, Envelope 6-8)
    - Bradford, Vt. - Piermont, N.H. (Box 5, Envelope 9-15)
    - Hanover, N.H. (Box 5, Envelope 16)
    - Conn. River - White River Junction (Box 5, Envelope 17-28)
    - Windsor - Ascutney, Vt. (Box 5, Envelope 29-44)
    - Claremont, N.H. Airport (Box 5, Envelope 45)
    - Charlestown, N.H. - Bellows Falls, Vt. (Box 5, Envelope 46-50)
    - Charlestown, N.H. - Bellows Falls, Vt. (Box 6, Envelope 51-64)
    - Brattleboro - Vernon, Vt. (Box 6, Envelope 65-81)
    - Turners Falls, Mass. (Box 6, Envelope 82-83)
    - Northampton, Mass. - (South. to North.) (Set No. 1) (Box 6, Envelope 84-100)
    - Northampton, Mass.- (Set No.1 Continued.) (Box 7, Envelope 101-103)
    - Nothampton, Mass. - (Set No.2) (Box 7, Envelope 104-129)
    - Northampton, Mass. - (Set No.3) (Box 7, Envelope 130-150)
    - Northampton, Mass. - (Set No.3 Continued.) (Box 8, Envelope 151-165)
    - Northampton, Mass. - (Set No. 4) (Box 8, Envelope 166-194)
    - Holyoke Dam - Springfield, Mass. (Box 8, Envelope 195-200)
    - Holyoke Dam - Springfield, Mass. (Box 9, Envelope 201-217)
    - Springfield, Mass. Airport (Box 9, Envelope 218)
    - Hartford, Conn. - (Set No. 1) (Box 9, Envelope 219-250)
    - Hartford, Conn. - (Set No. 1 Continued.) (Box 10, Envelope 251-258)
    - Hartford, Conn. - (Set No. 2) (Box 10, Envelope 259-267)
    - Middletown, Conn. - (Set No. 1) (Box 10, Envelope 268-296)
    - Middletown, Conn. - (Set No. 2) (Box 10, Envelope 297-303)
  - Mosaic Views, 1936; T001862
    - St. Johnsbury, Vt., 1 photograph (Box 20)
    - Bradford, Vt. - Piermont, N.H., 1 photograph (Box 20)
    - Conn. River - White River Junction, Vt., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Windsor - Ascutney, Vt., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Charlestown, N.H. - Bellows Falls, Vt., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Brattleboro - Vernon, Vt., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Turners Falls, Mass., 1 photograph (Box 20)
    - Northampton, Mass., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Holyoke Dam - Springfield, Mass., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Windsor Locks, Conn., 1 photograph (Box 20)
    - Hartford, Conn., 2 photographs (Box 20)
    - Middletown, Conn., 1 photograph (Box 20)
  - William Hankard Collection, 1936; T001765
    - East from under overpass on Asylum Street at railroad station (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - Looking east from railroad overpass on Asylum Street (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - From a point south of Asylum Street, Capitol in the distance (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - Bushnell Park south from Asylum Street (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Bond Hotel (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - High Street south (Box 21, Envelope 6)
    - Corner of High Street and Asylum Street south, Capitol in the distance (Box 21, Envelope 7)
    - Stonington Street east (Box 21, Envelope 8)
    - Two views of old Connecticut General Life Insurance Company (Box 21, Envelope 9)
    - State Street east from old trolley car trains corner of State and Market Streets (Box 21, Envelope 10)
    - The Hartford Times loading dock on Prospect Street (Box 21, Envelope 11)
    - Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 21, Envelope 12)
    - Talcott Street looking east from just below Main Street, Talcott Street east from corner of Market Street, Brown school (Box 21, Envelope 13)
    - Temple Street east from Market Street (Box 21, Envelope 14)
    - Looking east down Morgan Street from Main Street, National Guard on duty (Box 21, Envelope 15)
    - Colt's Park (Box 21, Envelope 16)
    - From atop G. Fox, looking east, northeast, southeast (Box 21, Envelope 17)
    - Unidentified (Box 21, Envelope 18)
  - A. B. Grasso Collection, 1936; T001765
    - Looking up Main Street, Terry's (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - The Southern New England Telephone Building (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - Pearl and High Streets (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - Two men near hotel (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Bushnell Park, overflow from park river (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - Looking toward Bushnell Park from railroad station (Box 21, Envelope 6)
    - Outside railroad station looking east (Box 21, Envelope 7)
    - Row of store fronts (Box 21, Envelope 8)
    - Cars in flooded parking lot (Box 21, Envelope 9)
    - Aerial view of city (Box 21, Envelope 10)
    - Four men next to boat (Box 21, Envelope 11)
    - Water pumps (Box 21, Envelope 12)
    - Pitkin Street, East Hartford (Box 21, Envelope 13)
    - House (Box 21, Envelope 14)
    - E. Lund's Garage, Prospect Street, East Hartford (Box 21, Envelope 15)
    - Connecticut General Life Insurance Company (Box 21, Envelope 16)
    - People in front of stores on flooded street (Box 21, Envelope 17)
    - Deep water (Box 21, Envelope 18)
    - Three boys on a boat in the road (Box 21, Envelope 19)
    - Man standing on top of car that is flooded up to the door (Box 21, Envelope 20)
    - Men standing next to boat (Box 21, Envelope 21)
    - Asylum Street from railroad station (Box 21, Envelope 22)
    - Asylum Street from corner of Ann Street (Box 21, Envelope 23)
    - Phoeniex Mutual Insurance Company (Box 21, Envelope 24)
    - Union Place and Asylum Street (Box 21, Envelope 25)
    - Corner of Prospect Street and Arch Street, Hartford Times to left (Box 21, Envelope 26)
    - Man standing in water (Box 21, Envelope 27)
    - Street scene (Box 21, Envelope 28)
    - Bushnell Park looking east, Jewell Street to left (Box 21, Envelope 29)
    - Two men (Box 21, Envelope 30)
    - The music shell Bushnell Park (Box 21, Envelope 31)
    - A submerged parking station (Box 21, Envelope 32)
    - Prospect Street, East Hartford (Box 21, Envelope 33)
    - Man floating down street on homemade raft (Box 21, Envelope 34)
    - Prospect Street, East Hartford (Box 21, Envelope 35)
    - Two men in front of building (Box 21, Envelope 36)
    - Two cars on street with rushing water (Box 21, Envelope 37)
    - Men and women standing in line (Box 21, Envelope 38)
    - Looking down Morgan Street to East Hartford Bridge (Box 21, Envelope 39)
  - Hartford Public Library Collection, 1936, T001765
    - State Street (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - Trumbull Street boat taking food to telephone company (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - Ann and Asylum Streets, Railroad station in the background (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - Hudson Street (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Flooded street scene (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - Looking into Asylum Street, Bushnell Park on right (Box 21, Envelope 6)
    - Ann Street south, Bushnell Park from corner of Pearl Street (Box 21, Envelope 7)
    - Union Place, Railroad station corner at left (Box 21, Envelope 8)
    - Pearl Street west (Box 21, Envelope 9)
    - Pearl Street west (Box 21, Envelope 9)
    - View of Bushnell Park, Elm Street to right (Box 21, Envelope 10)
    - Pearl Street, YMCA to the right (Box 21, Envelope 11)
    - Wall at Bolton Lake (Box 21, Envelope 12)
    - Ice on Bolton Lake (Box 21, Envelope 13)
    - Flooded house at Warehouse Pt. (Box 21, Envelope 14)
    - Warehouse Pt. Episcopal church (Box 21, Envelope 15)
    - Warehouse Pt. (Box 21, Envelope 16)
    - Windsor Locks Bridge taken at Warehouse Pt. (Box 21, Envelope 17)
    - Hartford scene (Box 21, Envelope 18)
    - Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 21, Envelope 19)
    - Connecticut Boulevard (Box 21, Envelope 20)
    - East Hartford High School (Box 21, Envelope 21)
    - Connecticut Boulevard (Box 21, Envelope 22)
    - Asylum Street (Box 21, Envelope 23)
    - Sheldon Street (Box 21, Envelope 24)
    - Tank in Wethersfield (Box 21, Envelope 25)
    - Bushnell Park (Box 21, Envelope 26)
    - Bushnell Park (Box 21, Envelope 27)
    - Windsor Locks Bridge (Box 21, Envelope 28)
    - Colt's Park (Box 21, Envelope 29)
    - Warehouse Pt. (Box 21, Envelope 30)
    - Asylum Street (Box 21, Envelope 31)
  - Harriet U. Fish Collection, 1936; T001765
    - High water in South Meadows, Wethersfield Cove; house in the middle (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - Overflow of Park River taken from end of Trumbull Street, Southern New England Telephone Company on right (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - South Meadows, Hartford Electric Light Company in distance, Brainard Aviation Field also in distance (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - Oil tanks in South Meadows off east of Wethersfield Ave. Power of water tipped tanks at queer angles even dislodged some (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Looking down Morgan Street Hill across Connecticut River Bridge to East Hartford (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - Looking up Asylum Street from railroad station, Bond Hotel in center, Bushnell Park on right caused by overflow of Park River, lobster Restaurant on left (Box 21, Envelope 6)
  - Mildred Davieau Collection, 1936; T001765
    - People working in kitcken (Box 21, Envelope 1)
    - Connecticut State Library (Box 21, Envelope 2)
    - State Armory (Box 21, Envelope 3)
    - St. Joseph's Cathedral (Box 21, Envelope 4)
    - Temple Beth Israel (Box 21, Envelope 5)
    - Connecticut State Capitol (Box 21, Envelope 6)
    - Wells and Hudson Street (Box 21, Envelope 7)
    - Aetna Insurance Company (Box 21, Envelope 8)
    - Connecticut General Life Insurance Company (Box 21, Envelope 9)
    - Sheldon Street near Main Street (Box 21, Envelope 10)
    - Southern New England Telephone Company (Box 21, Envelope 11)
    - Colt's Park (Box 21, Envelope 12)
    - Men standing and eating (Box 21, Envelope 13)
    - Trumbull Street to Bushnell Park (Box 21, Envelope 14)
    - Cafeteria line (Box 21, Envelope 15)
    - Information operators (Box 21, Envelope 16)
    - South Meadows Electric Light Plant (Box 21, Envelope 17)
    - Martial law, corner of Wethersfield Avenue and Wyllys Street (Box 21, Envelope 18)
- Series 2. Hurricane of 1938, T001765
  - Oblique Views, Numerical listing
    - Hartford and Vicinity
      - Hartford. Colt Building (Box 11, Envelope 1)
      - Hartford. St. Cyril's School; St. Peter's School; Trinity College Chapel (Box 11, Envelope 2)
      - Hartford. Downtown Hartford; Travelers Insurance Building (Box 11, Envelope 3)
      - Hartford. Capitol Building; State Theatre (Box 11, Envelope 4)
      - Hartford. P. Berry and Sons, 390 Windsor Street (Box 11, Envelope 5)
      - Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 6)
      - Hartford. Mayflower Upholstery Shop (Box 11, Envelope 7)
      - Hartford. Brainard Field; Hartford Electric Light Co; Colt Building (Box 11, Envelope 8)
      - Hartford. Founder's Bridge; Traveler's Building (Box 11, Envelope 9)
      - Hartford. Brainard Field; Hartford Electric Light Co; Colt Building (Box 11, Envelope 10)
      - Hartford. Hartford Electric Light Co. (Box 11, Envelope 11)
      - Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 12)
      - Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 13)
      - Hartford. Brainard Field (Box 11, Envelope 14)
      - Hartford. Brainard Field; Hartford Electric Light Co. (Box 11, Envelope 15)
      - Hartford. East Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 16)
      - Hartford. East Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 17)
      - East Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 18)
      - East Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 19)
      - East Hartford. Man in rowboat, water high up on telephone poles, reflections of houses on water (Box 11, Envelope 20)
      - East Hartford. The Great Gordon Tire Works, 110 Connecticut Blvd. (Box 11, Envelope 21)
      - East Hartford (Box 11, Envelope 22)
      - East Hartford. Airmarking, Pratt and Whitney Aircraft (Box 11, Envelope 23)
      - Wethersfield. Wethersfield Cove (Box 11, Envelope 24)
      - Wethersfield. Wethersfield Cove (Box 11, Envelope 25)
      - Wethersfield. Wethersfield Cove (Box 11, Envelope 26)
      - Cromwell (Box 11, Envelope 27)
    - Eastern & North Eastern Connecticut
      - Putnam. Airmarking (Box 11, Envelope 28)
      - Stafford. Stafford Springs (Box 11, Envelope 29)
      - Stafford. Stafford Springs (Box 11, Envelope 30)
      - Stafford. Stafford Springs; Bridge out (Box 11, Envelope 31)
      - Stafford. Stafford Springs (5 miles South of) (Box 11, Envelope 32)
      - Willington. Locomotive (Box 11, Envelope 33)
      - Willington. Airmarking (Box 11, Envelope 34)
      - Willington. Bridge out; Downed trees (Box 11, Envelope 35)
      - Mansfield. Eagleville; Storrs (Box 11, Envelope 36)
      - Ashford. West Ashford; Bridge out (Box 11, Envelope 37)
      - Ashford. Housing sinking (Box 11, Envelope 38)
      - Windham. Willimantic Pumping Station (Box 11, Envelope 39)
      - Windham. Willimantic Pumping Station (Box 11, Envelope 40)
      - Windham. Willimantic (Box 11, Envelope 41)
      - Windham. Willimantic; American Thread Co., factory and company housing (Box 11, Envelope 42)
      - Windham. Willimantic; (5 miles south of); Bridge gone; Trees down (Box 11, Envelope 43)
      - Windham. South Windham; Bridge washed out (Box 11, Envelope 44)
      - Scotland. Railroad bed washed out; notice sun's shadow through rails (Box 11, Envelope 45)
      - Sprague. Baltic; Factory and company housing; washed out bridge (Box 11, Envelope 46)
      - Sprague. Baltic, Factory and company housing; washed out bridge (Box 11, Envelope 47)
      - Sprague. Baltic; Factory and company housing; washed out bridge (Box 11, Envelope 48)
      - Norwich. Occum; Versailles (Box 11, Envelope 49)
      - Norwich. Occum; Versailles (Box 11, Envelope 50)
      - Norwich. Greenville (Box 11, Envelope 51)
      - Norwich. Taftville; Ponemah (Box 11, Envelope 52)
      - Norwich. Airmaking (Box 11, Envelope 53)
    - Connecticut Shore
      - East Haven (Box 11, Envelope 54)
      - East Haven (Box 11, Envelope 55)
      - East Haven. Momauguin (Box 11, Envelope 56)
      - East Haven. Momauguin (Box 11, Envelope 57)
      - East Haven. Momauguin (Box 11, Envelope 58)
      - Branford. Pine Orchard (Box 11, Envelope 59)
      - Branford. Island; shadow of plane in photo (Box 11, Envelope 60)
      - Branford. Island? (Box 11, Envelope 61)
      - Guilford. New construction, or destruction; Notice cornfield blown down (Box 11, Envelope 62)
      - Madison. Hogshead Pt; notice severe beach erosion (Box 11, Envelope 63)
      - Madison. Hogshead Pt. (Box 11, Envelope 64)
      - Madison (Box 11, Envelope 65)
      - Madison. Madison Surf Club vicinity (Box 11, Envelope 66)
      - Madison (Box 11, Envelope 67)
      - Madison (Box 11, Envelope 68)
      - Madison. Hammonasset State Park Pavillion (Box 11, Envelope 69)
      - Madison. Hammonasset State Park Pavillions (Box 11, Envelope 70)
      - Madison. Hammonasset State Park Pavillions (Box 12, Envelope 71)
      - Madison. Hammonasset State Park Pavillions (Box 12, Envelope 72)
      - Madison. Hammonasset State Park (Box 12, Envelope 73)
      - Clinton. Clinton Beach (Box 12, Envelope 74)
      - Clinton. Clinton Beach (Box 12, Envelope 75)
      - Clinton. Clinton Beach (Box 12, Envelope 76)
      - Clinton. Grove Beach (Box 12, Envelope 77)
      - Westbrook. Pine Brook (Box 12, Envelope 78)
      - Westbrook. Patchogue River; Singing Bridge (Box 12, Envelope 79)
      - Westbrook. Westbrook Beach (Box 12, Envelope 80)
      - Westbrook. Kelsy Point; House on roof upper left (Box 12, Envelope 81)
      - Old Saybrook. Saybrook (Box 12, Envelope 82)
      - Old Saybrook. Cornfield Point; Saybrook, CT (Box 12, Envelope 83)
      - Old Lyme. White Sands (Box 12, Envelope 84)
      - Old Lyme. Hawks Nest (Box 12, Envelope 85)
      - Old Lyme. Sound view; House in road (Box 12, Envelope 86)
      - Old Lyme. Sound View Beach (Box 12, Envelope 87)
      - Old Lyme. Point "O" Woods (Box 12, Envelope 88)
      - East Lyme. Rocky Neck (Box 12, Envelope 89)
      - East Lyme. Rocky Neck (Box 12, Envelope 90)
      - East Lyme. Black Point (Box 12, Envelope 91)
      - East Lyme. Black Point (Box 12, Envelope 92)
      - East Lyme. Niantic, Cresent Beach (Box 12, Envelope 93)
      - East Lyme. Niantic, Cresent Beach (Box 12, Envelope 94)
      - East Lyme. Niantic, Camp Cross (Box 12, Envelope 95)
      - Waterford (Box 12, Envelope 96)
      - New London. Osprey Beach (Box 12, Envelope 97)
      - New London. Ocean Beach (Box 12, Envelope 98)
      - New London. Ocean Beach (Box 12, Envelope 99)
      - New London. Ocean Beach (Box 12, Envelope 100)
      - New London (Box 12, Envelope 101)
      - New London (Box 12, Envelope 102)